fourthsource.com 2019-09-14

# Privacy and Cookie Policy - Fourth Source

This privacy policy sets out how Fourth Source uses and protects any information that you give Fourth Source when you use this website.

Fourth Source is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * name and job title
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails **** about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
  * **_We never pass your information onto any third parties_**

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, **** we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. For more information, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/).

**Cookies we use**

**Google Analytics** – We use this cookie to help us understand how visitors interact with our website, so we can deliver a better service for our users, all data is kept anonymous. You can find out more about Google’s privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/).

**Google Adsense –**  This cookie is used to help us understand how our ads on our website are performing and also deliver you the most relevant ads specifically to you. You can find out more about Google’s privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/).

**OpenX**  – This cookie is used to serve advertisements on the website. We use it to serve Google ads as well as our own ads. You can find out more about the OpenX cookie at [www.openx.com/about/openx-market-privacy-principles](https://www.openx.com/about/openx-market-privacy-principles).

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting.

If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to us at Fourth Source, 1 Lyric Square, London, W6 0NB.

Fourth Source may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1st January 2011.
